Finding Aid for Paul Winston McCracken papers, 1940-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence
  - 1981
    - W (Box 27)
  - 1982
    - A (Box 27)
    - American Enterprise Insitutute World Forum (Box 27)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy, 1982 (Box 27)
    - American Enterprises Institute Project on Neighborhood Revitalization, 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - B (Box 28)
    - C (Box 28)
    - Class Related Materials (Box 28)
    - Conference Board (Box 28)
    - Council of Economic Advisors, 1977-1982 (Box 28)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1980-1982 (Box 28)
    - D (Box 28)
    - Development Advisory Board, 1980-1982 (Box 28)
    - E (Box 28)
    - F (Box 28)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 28)
    - G (Box 28)
    - Government Departments (Box 28)
    - H (Box 28)
    - High Technology Task Force (Box 28)
    - I (Box 28)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Box 28)
    - J (Box 29)
    - Japanese Correspondence (Box 29)
    - K (Box 29)
    - L (Box 29)
    - M (Box 29)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 29)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 29)
    - Milliken Group (Box 29)
    - N (Box 29)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 29)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 29)
    - O (Box 29)
    - P (Box 29)
    - R (Box 29)
    - Recommendations (Box 29)
    - S (Box 29)
    - T (Box 29)
    - Tax Foundation Inc. (Box 29)
    - Technova (Box 29)
    - Technova Auto Study (1) (Box 29)
    - Technova Auto Study (2) (Box 30)
    - U (Box 30)
    - V (Box 30)
    - W (Box 30)
    - Y (Box 30)
    - Z (Box 30)
  - 1983
    - A (Box 30)
    - Albion College (Box 30)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 30)
    - B (Box 30)
    - Brookings Institution, 1977-1983 (Box 30)
    - C (Box 30)
    - D (Box 30)
    - E (Box 30)
    - F (Box 30)
    - Feldstein, Martin (includes earlier material) (Box 30)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 30)
    - G (Box 30)
    - Government Departments (Box 30)
    - H (Box 30)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) (Box 30)
    - IMDI Fowler-McCracken Committee (Box 30)
    - J (Box 30)
    - Japanese Correspondence (Box 30)
    - K (Box 31)
    - L (Box 31)
    - M (Box 31)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 31)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 31)
    - Michigan, University of, Capital Campaign (Box 31)
    - N-O (Box 31)
    - P-Q (Box 31)
    - R (Box 31)
    - S (Box 31)
    - T (Box 31)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 31)
    - Technova (Box 31)
    - Teramura, Soji (Box 31)
    - U-V (Box 31)
    - W-Z (Box 31)
  - 1984
    - A (Box 31)
    - Albion College (Box 31)
    - American Enterprise Institute (AEI) (Box 31)
    - AEI Neighborhood Revitalization (Box 31)
    - B (Box 31)
    - C (Box 31)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 31)
    - Congressional Budget Office, 1977-1984 (Box 31)
    - D (Box 32)
    - E (Box 32)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 32)
    - F (Box 32)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 32)
    - G (Box 32)
    - German Marshall Fund (Box 32)
    - Government Departments (Box 32)
    - Government: House and Senate (Box 32)
    - Government: Joint Council on Economic Education (Box 32)
    - H-I (Box 32)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) (Box 32)
    - IMDI Fowler-McCracken Committee (Box 32)
    - J (Box 32)
    - Japanese Correspondence (Box 32)
    - K (Box 32)
    - L (Box 32)
    - M (Box 32)
    - Michigan Leadership (Box 32)
    - N (Box 32)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 32)
    - National Tax Limitation Committee (Box 32)
    - O-P (Box 32)
    - Personal (McCracken) (Box 32)
    - R (Box 32)
    - Reagan (includes earlier material) (Box 32)
    - S (Box 32)
    - Simon, Bill (Box 32)
    - Spivey, W. Allen (Box 32)
    - T (Box 32)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 32)
    - Technova (Box 32)
    - U-V (Box 32)
    - W (Box 32)
    - Y-Z (Box 32)
  - 1985
    - A (Box 33)
    - Albion College (Box 33)
    - B (Box 33)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 33)
    - C (Box 33)
    - D (Box 33)
    - E (Box 33)
    - F (Box 33)
    - Foreign Correspondence (Box 33)
    - G (Box 33)
    - German Marshall Fund (Box 33)
    - Global Economic Action Institute (Box 33)
    - Government Departments (Box 33)
    - H (Box 33)
    - I (Box 33)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) (Box 33)
    - J (Box 33)
    - K (Box 33)
    - L (Box 33)
    - M (Box 33)
    - Memoranda Received (Box 33)
    - Memoranda Sent (Box 33)
    - N (Box 33)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 33)
    - O (Box 33)
    - P-Q (Box 33)
    - Personal (McCracken) (Box 33)
    - R (Box 33)
    - S (Box 33)
    - T (Box 33)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 33)
    - Technova (Box 33)
    - U-V,W (Box 33)
    - X-Z (Box 33)
  - 1986
    - A-E (Box 34)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 34)
    - Biggs/Gilmore (Box 34)
    - Citations (Box 34)
    - Commitments and Expenses (Box 34)
    - Dow Chemical (Box 34)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 34)
    - Economic Club of Traverse City (Box 34)
    - Economic Dinner Group (Box 34)
    - F-H (Box 34)
    - Faculty Bibliography, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Federal Reserve System Board of Governors (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Foreign (Box 34)
    - Fund for America's Future (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Honorary Degree Committee (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Hoover Institute (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Hoover Universal (Box 34)
    - House Wednesday Group (Box 34)
    - International Management and Development Group (Box 34)
    - Japan (Box 34)
    - Johnson Controls (Box 34)
    - K-M (Box 34)
    - K Mart Corp. (Box 34)
    - Lincoln National (Box 34)
    - Memorandum Received (Box 34)
    - Memorandum Sent (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 34)
    - N-W (Box 34)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 34)
    - Sara Lee Corp. (Box 34)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 34)
  - 1987
    - A-D (Box 34)
    - Albion College (Box 34)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 34)
    - American Banking Association (Task Force on Inflation) (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Chen, Kan (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 34)
    - Corporate Boards (Box 34)
    - Council on International Exchange (Box 34)
    - E-H (Box 34)
    - German Marshall Fund (includes earlier material) (Box 34)
    - Foreign (Box 34)
    - Ford Library (Box 34)
    - Gerald Ford Institute (Box 34)
    - Government (Box 34)
    - International Management and Development Institute, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Japanese (Box 35)
    - K-P (Box 35)
    - Memorandum Received (Box 35)
    - Memorandum Sent (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 35)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 35)
    - Q-W (Box 35)
    - Recommendations (Box 35)
    - Technova (includes earlier material) (Box 35)
  - 1988
    - A-E (Box 35)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 35)
    - Colleges (includes earlier material) (Box 35)
    - Conference Board (Box 35)
    - Congress and Senate (includes earlier material) (Box 35)
    - Corporate Boards (Box 35)
    - Council on International Exchange (Box 35)
    - Earhart Foundation (includes earlier material) (Box 35)
    - F-R (Box 35)
    - Foreign (Box 35)
    - Government (Box 35)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 35)
    - S-Z (Box 35)
    - Technova (Box 35)
  - 1989
    - A-H (Box 35)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 35)
    - Corporate Boards (Box 35)
    - Economic Dinner Club (Box 35)
    - Embassies and consulates (Box 35)
    - Foreign (Box 35)
    - Government (Box 35)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Box 35)
    - L-N (Box 35)
    - Memoranda (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 35)
    - O-Z (Box 35)
    - Technova (Box 35)
  - 1990
    - A-H (Box 35)
    - Congress and Senate (Box 35)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 35)
    - Federal Reserve System (Box 35)
    - Government Regulation (Box 35)
    - Foreign (Box 35)
    - General Motors (includes earlier material) (Box 35)
    - Government (Box 35)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 35)
    - International Management and Development Institution (Box 35)
    - International Management and Development Institution--Europe Meeting (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 35)
    - Institute for International Economics (Box 36)
    - Invitations (Box 36)
    - J (Box 36)
    - Japanese (Box 36)
    - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (Box 36)
    - Johnson Controls (Box 36)
    - Joint Council on Economic Relations (Box 36)
    - K (Box 36)
    - K-Mart (Box 36)
    - L-Mc (Box 36)
    - Memorandums (Box 36)
    - Monetary Policy Forum (Box 36)
    - Mont Pelerin Society (Box 36)
    - National Association of Business Economists (Box 36)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (Box 36)
    - Nihon Keizai Shinbun (Box 36)
    - News Releases (Box 36)
    - N-P (Box 36)
    - Presbyterian Church (Box 36)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 36)
    - Q-R (Box 36)
    - Recommendation Letters (Box 36)
    - S (Box 36)
    - Sara Lee (Box 36)
    - Shumpeter SocietySenate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 36)
    - T (Box 36)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 36)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 36)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 36)
    - Troy State University (Box 36)
    - U-X (Box 36)
    - William Penn College (Box 36)
    - Wright Investors (Box 36)
    - Y-Z (Box 36)
  - 1991
    - A (Box 36)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 36)
    - Albion College (Box 36)
    - B (Box 36)
    - Berea College (Box 36)
    - Biggs/Gillmore (Box 36)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 36)
    - C (Box 36)
    - Conference Board (Box 36)
    - Cosmos Club (Box 36)
    - D (Box 36)
    - Dow Chemical Co. (Box 36)
    - E (Box 36)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 36)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 36)
    - Economic Dinner Group (Box 36)
    - F (Box 36)
    - Fax's (Box 36)
    - G (Box 36)
    - German Marshall Fund of the United States (Box 36)
    - Greater Detroit & Windsor (Box 36)
    - H (Box 36)
    - I (Box 36)
    - International Automotive Industry Forum (Box 36)
    - J (Box 36)
    - K (Box 36)
    - Kmart (Box 36)
    - L (Box 36)
    - M (Box 36)
    - Mc (Box 36)
    - N (Box 36)
    - National Association of Business Economics (Box 36)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (Box 36)
    - O (Box 36)
    - P (Box 36)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 36)
    - Q-R (Box 36)
    - S (Box 36)
    - Sara Lee (Box 36)
    - Schempeter Society (Box 36)
    - Scientific Club (Box 36)
    - Society Bank (Box 36)
    - T (Box 36)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 36)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 36)
    - U-V (Box 36)
    - University Library (Box 36)
    - The University Musical Society of the U of M (Box 36)
    - Viravan Letters (Box 36)
    - W-X (Box 36)
    - William Penn College (Box 36)
    - Wright Investors (Box 36)
    - Y-Z (Box 36)
  - 1992
    - A (Box 36)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 36)
    - Albion College (Box 36)
    - B (Box 36)
    - Berea College (Box 36)
    - William Biggs/Gilmore (Box 36)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 36)
    - Brookings Institute (Box 36)
    - C (Box 38)
    - Conference Board (Box 38)
    - D (Box 38)
    - Dow Chemical Co. (Box 38)
    - Dunworkin Club (Box 38)
    - E (Box 38)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 38)
    - Economic Dinner Group (Box 38)
    - F (Box 38)
    - G (Box 38)
    - Gerstacker Honorary Degree Letters (Box 38)
    - German Marshall Fund (Box 38)
    - Greater Detroit and Windsor Japan-America Committee (Box 38)
    - H (Box 38)
    - I (Box 38)
    - International Automotive Industry Forum (Box 38)
    - International Management and Development Institute (Box 38)
    - J (Box 38)
    - K (Box 38)
    - Kmart (Box 38)
    - L (Box 38)
    - Mc (Box 38)
    - N (Box 38)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 38)
    - O (Box 38)
    - Office for the study of Aumotive Transportation (U of M) (Box 38)
    - P (Box 38)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 38)
    - Q-R (Box 38)
    - S (Box 38)
    - Sara Lee (Box 38)
    - Seidman Letters (Box 38)
    - T (Box 38)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 38)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 38)
    - U-V (Box 38)
    - University Library (Box 38)
    - W-X (Box 38)
    - William Penn College (Box 38)
    - Y-Z (Box 38)
  - 1993
    - A (Box 38)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 38)
    - Albion College (Box 38)
    - B (Box 38)
    - Berea College (Box 38)
    - Biggs/Gilmore (Box 38)
    - Bretton Woods Committee (Box 38)
    - C (Box 38)
    - Center for Public Choice George Mason University (Box 38)
    - D (Box 38)
    - Davidson College (Box 38)
    - E (Box 39)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 39)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 39)
    - Economic Dinner Group (Box 39)
    - F (Box 39)
    - G (Box 39)
    - German Marshall Fund of the United States (Box 39)
    - H (Box 39)
    - Hoover Institute (Box 39)
    - I (Box 39)
    - International Industrial Development Foundation (Box 39)
    - International Automotive Industry Forum (Box 39)
    - International Management and Development (Box 39)
    - J (Box 39)
    - K (Box 39)
    - L (Box 39)
    - M (Box 39)
    - Mc (Box 39)
    - McInally Lecture Letters (Box 39)
    - N (Box 39)
    - National Association of Business Economists (Box 39)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 39)
    - O (Box 39)
    - Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (U of M) (Box 39)
    - P (Box 39)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 39)
    - Q-R (Box 39)
    - Rice Univeristy (Box 39)
    - S (Box 39)
    - T (Box 39)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 39)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 39)
    - U-V (Box 39)
    - W-X (Box 39)
    - Wright Investors' (Box 39)
    - William Penn College (Box 39)
    - Y-Z (Box 39)
  - 1994
    - A (Box 39)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 39)
    - B (Box 39)
    - Berea College (Box 39)
    - C (Box 39)
    - Claremont Graduate School (Box 39)
    - D (Box 39)
    - E (Box 39)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 39)
    - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 39)
    - F (Box 39)
    - G (Box 39)
    - German Marshall Fund (Box 39)
    - Hoover Institute (Box 39)
    - H (Box 39)
    - I (Box 39)
    - International Management & Development Institute (Box 39)
    - J (Box 39)
    - Joint Economic Committee Congress of the U.S. (Box 39)
    - Biggs/Gilmore (Box 39)
    - K (Box 39)
    - Kmart (Box 39)
    - L (Box 39)
    - M (Box 39)
    - Mc (Box 39)
    - N (Box 40)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research (Box 40)
    - O-P (Box 40)
    - Public Oversight Board (Box 40)
    - Q-S (Box 40)
    - Sara Lee (Box 40)
    - T (Box 40)
    - Tax Foundation (Box 40)
    - Texas Instruments (Box 40)
    - U-V (Box 40)
    - W (Box 40)
    - William Penn College (Box 40)
    - XYZ (Box 40)
  - 1995
    - C (Box 40)
    - Center for Media and Public Affairs (Box 40)
    - Center for the Study of Presidency (Box 40)
    - Center for Study of Public Choice George Mason University (Box 40)
    - Claremont Graduate School (Box 40)
    - D (Box 40)
    - E (Box 40)
    - The Economic Club of Florida (Box 40)
    - Earhart Foundation (Box 40)
    - F (Box 40)
    - G (Box 40)
    - H (Box 40)
    - I (Box 40)
    - J (Box 40)
    - K (Box 40)
    - L (Box 40)
    - M (Box 40)
    - N (Box 40)
    - Richard Nixon Library (Box 40)
    - O (Box 40)
    - P (Box 40)
    - R (Box 40)
    - S (Box 40)
    - T (Box 40)
    - U (Box 40)
    - W (Box 40)
    - William Penn College (Box 40)
    - Wright Investors Service (Box 40)
    - XYZ (Box 40)
    - Fort Worth, TX Lecture (Box 40)
  - 1996
    - A (Box 40)
    - American Enterprise Institute (Box 40)
    - Albion College (Box 40)
    - B-C (Box 40)
    - Citizens Research Council of Michigan (Box 40)
    - Cosmos Club (Box 40)
    - Council of Economic Advisers (Box 40)
    - D-E (Box 40)
    - Economic Dinner Group (Box 40)
    - F (Box 40)
    - G (Box 40)
    - H (Box 40)
    - I (Box 40)
    - International Management & Development Institute (Box 40)
    - J (Box 40)
    - K (Box 40)
    - L (Box 40)
    - M (Box 40)
    - Mc (Box 40)
    - N (Box 40)
    - O (Box 40)
    - P (Box 40)
    - R (Box 40)
    - S (Box 40)
    - T (Box 40)
    - U-V (Box 40)
    - W-Z (Box 40)
  - 1997
    - A (Box 41)
    - B (Box 41)
    - C (Box 41)
    - D (Box 41)
    - E (Box 41)
    - F (Box 41)
    - G (Box 41)
    - H (Box 41)
    - I (Box 41)
    - J (Box 41)
    - K (Box 41)
    - L (Box 41)
    - M (Box 41)
    - N (Box 41)
    - O (Box 41)
    - P (Box 41)
    - R (Box 41)
    - S (Box 41)
    - T (Box 41)
    - U-V (Box 41)
    - W (Box 41)
    - XYZ (Box 41)
  - 1998
    - A (Box 41)
    - B (Box 41)
    - C (Box 41)
    - D (Box 41)
    - E (Box 41)
    - F (Box 41)
    - G (Box 41)
    - H (Box 41)
    - J (Box 41)
    - K (Box 41)
    - L (Box 41)
    - M (Box 41)
    - N (Box 41)
    - O (Box 41)
    - P (Box 41)
    - R (Box 41)
    - S (Box 41)
    - T (Box 41)
    - U (Box 41)
    - V (Box 41)
    - W (Box 41)
    - XYZ (Box 41)
  - 1999
    - A (Box 41)
    - B (Box 41)
    - C (Box 41)
    - E (Box 41)
    - F (Box 41)
    - G (Box 41)
    - H (Box 41)
    - J (Box 41)
    - K (Box 41)
    - L (Box 41)
    - M (Box 41)
    - N (Box 41)
    - O (Box 41)
    - P (Box 41)
    - R (Box 41)
    - S (Box 41)
    - T (Box 41)
    - UVW (Box 41)
    - XYZ (Box 41)
  - 2000-2004
    - A (Box 41)
    - Vinay Bharat-Ram Dinner (Box 41)
    - B (Box 41)
    - C (Box 41)
    - Coleman, Mary Sue (Box 41)
    - D (Box 41)
    - E (Box 41)
    - F (Box 41)
    - G (Box 41)
    - H (Box 41)
    - I (Box 41)
    - J (Box 41)
    - K (Box 41)
    - L (Box 41)
    - M (Box 41)
    - N (Box 41)
    - O (Box 41)
    - P (Box 41)
    - R (Box 41)
    - S (Box 41)
    - T (Box 41)
    - U-W (Box 41)
    - X-Z (Box 41)
- Publicity and Speeches
  The Publicity and Speeches series contains unpublished speeches as well as published speeches, and papers. Additionally, a large part of the series is dedicated to newspaper clippings and magazine articles containing publicity on McCracken's career at the Federal Reserve Bank, as a member of the U.S. Council of Economic Advisors, as a Professor at the University of Michigan and as an economic expert.
  - Undated 1942-1970 (Box 12)
  - 1971-1983 (Box 13)
  - Published interviews, 1969-1971 (Box 13)
  - Clippings, 1968-1984, 2 folders (Box 13)
    (mainly accounts of talks)
  - Clippings, 1945-2000 (scattered, mostly 1950s-1980s), 9 folders (Box 45)
  - Ann Arbor Regional Business-to-Business, October 2001 (Box 45)
  - Ann Arbor Scene Magazine, 1975Business Forum, July-August 1972 (Box 45)
  - Business Conditions, 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - Business Week, August 23, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Business Week, August 8, 1970 (Box 45)
  - Business Week, January 18, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Business Week, December 1, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, the Magazine of the Graduate School of Business Administration, winter 1972 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, fall 1973 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, fall 1974 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, winter 1979 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, September 1996 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, fall 1998 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, spring 2007 (Box 45)
  - Dividend, spring 2011 (Box 45)
  - Economic Outlook USA, 1974 (Box 45)
  - Fortune Magazine, July 1969 (Box 45)
  - Fortune Magazine, May 1970 (Box 45)
  - Fortune Magazine, June 1972 (Box 45)
  - Hayes-Albion Corporation Annual Report, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Life (International), March 22, 1965 (Box 45)
  - Life (International), February 7, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Manufacturers Hanover Trust "The Schizophrenic Economic Outlook," 1967 (Box 45)
  - Michigan Investor, 1977 (Box 45)
  - Monroe Street Journal, October 5, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Mortgage Banker, The, April 1969 (Box 45)
  - Neurotic Trillionaire: A Survey of Mr. Nixon's America, May 10, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, February 3, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, January 27, 1969 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, January 18, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, January 25, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, December 6, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Newsweek, September 30, 1974 (Box 45)
  - Notes: School of Business Administration (Emory University), 1967 (Box 45)
  - Notes (University of Michigan Musical Society), fall 1998 (Box 45)
  - Production, March 1981 (Box 45)
  - Synchronizer, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - Time Magazine, December 6, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Time Magazine, August 19, 1974 (Box 45)
  - University of Michigan News and Info Press Release, November 24, 1971 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, November 18, 1968 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, April 28, 1969 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, March 3, 1969 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, January 12, 1970 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, July 26, 1971 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, August 30, 1971 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, December 6, 1971 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, August 19, 1974 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, August 26, 1974 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, February 21, 1977 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, February 6, 1978 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, March 17, 1980 (Box 45)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Women's Club of Ann Arbor, March 1977 (Box 45)
- U.S. Dept. of Commerce. National Economic Unit
  The U.S. Dept. of Commerce National Economic Unit series contains memoranda dating from McCracken's involvement with this unit.
  - Memoranda, 1943 (Box 14)
- President's Council of Economic Advisors
  The President's Council of Economic Advisors series contains a small file of McCracken memoranda from the period during the Eisenhower administration when he was a member of the Council. There is substantially more material from the period of his chairmanship of the CEA during the Nixon administration. Included are memoranda regarding federal economic policy, reports and studies, published materials and newspaper clippings.
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1969 Trip to Japan, July 1969 (Box 14)
  - Memos to the White House
    - 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - January 1969-December 1970, 24 folders (Box 14)
    - January 1971-December 1971, 12 folders (Box 15)
  - Economic Outlook: 1969
    - Troika, January-June 1969 (Box 15)
    - Troika, July-December 1969 (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, January-June 1969 (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, July-December 1969 (Box 15)
    - Budget (Box 15)
    - Unemployment v. Prices (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Economic Outlook: 1970
    - Troika (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, January-June 1970 (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, July-September 1970 (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, October-December 1970 (Box 15)
    - Budget (Box 15)
    - Unemployment v. Prices, January-June, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Unemployment v. Prices, July-December 1970 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Economic Outlook: 1971
    - Troika (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, January-June 1971 (Box 15)
    - CEA Gross National Product Projections, July-December 1971 (Box 15)
    - Budget (Box 15)
    - Unemployment v. Prices (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - December 1968-July 1971, 41 folders (Box 16)
  - Notes on various economic meetings
    - Current Outlook, notes (Box 16)
    - 1959-1962, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - 1964-1967, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Economic Outlook, Notes on Meetings, 1963-1981, 5 folders (Box 16)
- Papers, 1945-1996